翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Two lectures ago, we built the IntList.
前两节课我们创建了 IntList
It was a really beautiful, recursive data structure,
这是一个非常漂亮的递归数据结构
very pure.
非常纯粹
And it allows us to store any amount of information
它允许我们存储任意数量的信息
so long as we're willing to keep adding nodes at the end
只要我们愿意在末尾不断增加节点
and our computer doesn't run out of memory.
并且我们的电脑不会内存不足
So while they're powerful, they have the issue that they're a little awkward to work with.
虽然它们很强大，但有一个难以处理的问题
If you want to add to the beginning or the end,
如果你想在开头或结尾添加
you have to do direct pointer manipulation.
就必须进行直接指针操作
And so what we showed in the previous lecture
我们在上一节课中所展示的
was how to add a layer of bureaucracy and produce the SLList,
就是如何增加一层官僚主义，产生了 SLList
where now we have a middleman that we go to manipulate the list.
现在我们有一个中间人去操纵 List
So, for example, suppose I want to add to the front of the list.
例如，假设我想要添加到 List 的前面
I go to the middle man, and I say, hey, please add first.
我去找中间人说：“嘿，请加到前面”
And then maybe what she'll do is well, whatever magic stuff the SLList does.
也许她会做的很好，不管 SLList 做什么神奇的东西
We don't need to care about it as the user of an SLList.
作为 SLList 的用户，我们不需要关心它
We simply call the methods of the SLList class.
只需调用 SLList 类的方法
So we enumerated a number of improvements.
然后我们列举了一些改进措施
And now that brings us to this moment,
把我们带到了这个时刻
where we're going to improve the SLList yet more.
我们将进一步改进 SLList
So there's some obvious limitations to the SLList,
SLList 有一些明显的限制
like the version we have right now,
就像我们现在的版本
you cannot add to the middle.
你不能添加到中间
And we could add those features,
我们可以添加这些功能
but there's actually a more fundamental issue that I'd like to tackle.
但实际上有一个更根本的问题，我想解决
And that is the fact that adding to the back is slow.
添加到末尾真的很慢
So if we think about how we add to the end of an SLList,
考虑一下如何添加到 SLList 的末尾
inside under the hood what a SLList does
SLList 在内部所做的
is it iterates through all of the items
就是遍历所有的项
and then finally sets the next pointer.
然后最后设置 next 指针
Now that is going to be slow because we have to iterate to this list much like we saw with the size method before.
慢的原因是我们需要遍历整个 List，就像之前的 size 方法一样
So you might think, inspired by what we did with the size method,
所以在处理 size 方法的启发下
about ways that we could improve our SLList
我们如何改进 SLList
so that add last is also fast.
让在末尾添加也很快
So ponder that for a moment and maybe pause.
暂停仔细考虑一下
OK.
好
So perhaps you've thought about it.
也许你已经考虑过了
An you thought, how do we make size fast?
你想我们怎么让 size 变快的呢？
Well we cache the size, so maybe I could just cache the last pointer.
我们缓存了 size，也许也可以缓存 last 指针
So I would have the size, a sentinel node here,
在这里有 size、一个哨兵节点
and the last pointer pointing at the last node.
还有 指向最后一个节点的 last 指针
So let's think about all the things you might want to do with a list.
让我们考虑一下你可能想用 List 做的所有事情
You want to add to it, get stuff from it, remove it.
你想要添加、获取、删除
Now we're going to think big.
现在我们有更大的想法
We're going to ponder, if we have a last pointer, is that enough?
我们要考虑的是，有 last 指针就够了吗？
Is that enough so that all of these operations will be fast?
这足够让所有操作都很快吗？
And if not, which one will be slow?
如果不是，哪一个会慢呢？
So I'm not going to spoil that in this video,
我不会在这段视频中说
but I'd like you to ponder that on your own.
我想让你自己思考一下
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）